PERSONAL PARTICULAR

Name TEH YEE CHUN

Correspondence MK9, Kampung Parit Teriman

Address 83200 Senggarang

Batu Pahat, Johor

Gender Female

Citizenship Malaysian and Singapore Permanent Residence

Birthday 10th August 1991

Status Single

Phone (mobile) 017-8246011

Email leochun 0810@hotmail.com

Availability Immediate

Expected Salary SGD 3,000 (negotiable)

Last Drawn Salary SGD 2,600



OBJECTIVE

Reliable and dedicated audit assistant with around 3 years of experience in auditing of comprehensive environment and financial statements preparation. Seeking to leverage my technical and professional expertise to grow in the new role of Accounts Associate/Assistant at your company.

EDUCATION

June 2010 to June 2014 Bachelor of Accounting (Hons)

Multimedia University, Melaka

CGPA 3.45 / 4.0

June 2009 to June 2010 Foundation in Management

Multimedia University, Melaka

CGPA 3.46 / 4.0

January 2004 to Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

December 2008 Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Senggarang, Johor

WORKING EXPERIENCE

1. K.C.CHAN & CO. PAC (October 2014 – June 2017)

Audit Assistant

- ✓ Conducts assigned audit engagements from audit planning towards audit completion and ensure engagements are completed on time.
- ✓ Identifies and communicates issues arises with audit partner, involve in meeting together with audit partner in resolving issues noted in audit fieldwork and offering recommended solutions for audit client.
- ✓ Involved in group audit, liaising with audit client and communicates among engagement team in a manner that is clear and concise ensuring the consistencies of accounting policies adopted by the group and resolve any issue arise during the group audit.
- ✓ Assist and provide guidance to new staffs.
- ✓ Involved in audit and assurance engagement in various industries (i.e. trading, retail, F&B, investment, construction).

2. D.R.SENG & CO. (March 2013 to August 2013)

Vacation Trainee

- ✓ Involved in statutory audit for investment companies and trading companies.
- ✓ Liaising with managerial staff.
- ✓ Ensure procedures, policies, legislation and regulations are correctly followed and complied with.
- ✓ Performed analytical review and detailed substantive test for all the sections in Financial Statements.

EXTRA CO-CURICULAR ACTIVITIES

University Level Exco Member MMU Japanese Language Society –

Japanese Culture Fair 2010/2011

Treasurer MMU Japanese Language Society –

Bon-Odori

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office Suite proficiency
- SQL Accounting Software
- Audit Reporting
- External Audit
- Spoken and written language : English, Mandarin and Malay

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- 1. Possess positive working attitude, responsible, cheerful and energetic personality.
- 2. Able to work independently as well as a team player.
- 3. Fast learner and able to handle multiple task.
- 4. Willing to learn new skills and knowledge to explore my career.
- 5. Possess good interpersonal and communication skill.
- 6. Enjoy working in fast-paced environment